flirtandsex.com 2013-11-21

# Live Cams | Webcam Video Chat | Flirt and Sex with these Single Girls

__**S U M M A R Y :**__

             • We NEVER sell, rent or share your personal information or email address with any other party.

             • We may send you occasional promotional emails, and every email will contain an unsubscribe option.

             • Your personal information is never stored on our servers, so it cannot be stolen by hackers.

_Below are the complete details of our privacy policy:_

_**I.    **_**N O T I C E:**__

**  (a). What personal information we collect and how we use your information:**

          When you visit our web site, we capture the internet provider's domain name and country that you came from (e.g., 'aol.com') and

          the paths taken as you move from page to page (i.e., your "click stream" activity).       

          Information we collect may be used to enhance your use of this web site in ways like these:

             • Arrange the web site in the most user-friendly way

             • Customize your browsing experience of this web site

             • Communicate special offers and featured items to you, if you choose to receive such notices

             • Respond to your question or suggestions

**  (b). Email, Mailing Lists, and Other Services:**

          When you submit your email address on a form at this website, or send an email to a model on this website, your email address may be used

          to send you occasional promotional material about Service and Newsletter. Submitting your email address is always optional. If you choose to

          disclose your address, it will never be abused or used in an irresponsible manner. For example, we will not "spam" you or send you frequent

          promotional  emails. Emails will never contain adult material, although they may contain promotions for adult material. Your email address will

          NEVER be sold, rented or shared with any outside party. Every email you receive from Our website will contain an unsubscribe option.

**  (c). Visitor Registration or Requests for Information:**

          Administration site only collects personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when making purchases or applying for special

          offers at the web site. "Personal information" includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name (but not

          your email address). While you can browse our site without providing any personal information, you will need to submit certain information in

          order  to take advantage of free promotions, or to make purchases.

          Administration website will never ask you for the personal information of others. When completing any form that requests personal

          information, it is expected that you will provide your own information, and never that of another individual.

**  (d). Browsing and the use of Cookies:**

          Our website uses cookie technology for the basic functionality of the website, such as it's appearance (e.g. color scheme). If you visited

          our website by clicking on a link at an affiliate website, then the affiliate's unique ID is also stored in a cookie. Cookies do not capture your

          email address or ANY private information about you. It necessary to have cookies enabled to browse the website. See the "Help" section

          of your browser if you need to enable cookies.We also use standard web server log files to help us count visitors and evaluate our site's

          technical capacity. We use this information to find out how many people visit Our website, help us arrange the pages in the most user-friendly

          way, keep the site browser-friendly, and to make our pages more useful to our visitors. We record information on site traffic but not

          information on individual visitors to our site, so no information about you in particular will be kept or used.

**  (e). «Sex» Games, Surveys and Other Promotions:**

          From time to time, Administration website may conduct «sex» games, surveys or other promotions via our web site. If you choose to

          participate, we use your response to select winners, to come up with the game or survey results and, sometimes, to publish those results in

          aggregate on the site. We will hold only as anonymous statistics. We will never sell or rent such information to any third parties.

**    (f). Linking To Other Sites:**

          Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another web site, the Our website Rules and this Privacy Policy

          are no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including any site that has a link on our website, is subject to

          the rules and policies of that site. We encourage you to read the rules and policies of the sites you visit to further understand their

          procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

**  (g). Our policy regarding sharing of information:**

          Administration website will NEVER sell, rent or share your private information with any outside party, under any circumstances.The only

          possible exception to this policy is where disclosure is required by law, for example a court order.

_**II.    **_**C H O I C E :**__

**    (a). How you can decide what communication you'll receive from us:**

          If you submit your email address at any form on this website, Administration website may periodically send you email messages describing

          updates, new features, or promotional offers related to this web site. You can choose to stop receiving this email at any time. Simply follow

          the instructions included in your email, or send a reply stating your request. Such responses should be sent to the sender's address

          (on most email programs you can simply click "Reply") to ensure prompt removal.

_**III.    **_**A C C E S S :**__

**    (a). How to update or correct your personal information:**

           To modify or delete your personal information, simply follow the instructions included in your email, or send a reply stating your request,

           and we will make the requested changes.

_**IV.    **_**S E C U R I T Y :**__

**     (a). How we protect the security of your personal information:**

            The security of your personal information is very important to us and we are committed to protecting the information we collect.

            Administration website uses advanced security measures to protect its website and computer assets. Most importantly, your personal

            credit card information isnot stored on our website, and therefore cannot be stolen even if a security breach occurs.

_**V.    **_**C U S T O M E R    S E R V I C E   and   R E C O U R S E :**__

**     (a). Changes to the Privacy Policy:**

           Administration website reserves the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. Please also read over the our Site Rules.

           Administration website takes privacy matters very seriously, and intends to stay at the forefront of privacy policy and protection matters.

           Administration will occasionally update our privacy policy and we will post those updates on this page. You are responsible for revisiting

           page to review our privacy policy updates.

**      (b). How to contact us:**

           Please note that whenever you submit any information to us in connection with any related services, you consent to processing of this

           information in the United States as necessary to provide the services in which you are participating. If you have any questions,

           comments or complaints about Site privacy policy and/or the way it affects you, please feel free to [Contact Us](http://flirtandsex.com/page/frequently-asked-questions)

_**VI.    **_**F E E S ,    C R E D I T   C O M P E N S A T I O N ,   R E F U N D  and  U N L A W F U L   C O N D U C T :**__

**      (a). The subscribers may purchase credit packages to spend in the available areas of Adult Entertainment;** therefore the selection of services

            must be preceded of the consultation by the Subscriber of the correspondent content, price list and means of payment made available

            on the website.

**      (b). Text chat with the dressed Adult Service Providers is free, but if a subscriber wants to access the full feature service** (including

            undressed  Adult Service Providers and private show) he/she must click on “Enter Private Session” button and from that point on stays in the

            video chat room  with the Adult Service Provider entering into a private mode where the purchased credits are used on a per-minute basis.

**     (c). Billing of a given account** (the actual price payable for credit packages) depends on the physical location where the account has been

            created.

**      (d). In case of any query to Our Authorized Sales Agents** will be able to help you regarding your transactions made through payments provider

       as well, by contacting the provider in question. Therefore, for billing information and support the following contacts should be used:

                  \- [PAYSITE-CASH.COM](https://billing.paysite-cash.biz/customers/?site=3969)  
                  \- [EPOCH.COM](https://epoch.com/billingsupport)  
                  \- [CCBill.COM](https://support.ccbill.com/)

            Site **Administration** does not store nor has access to transaction details.

**      (e). For banking expenses information, each subscriber should consult directly his/her bank.**

**      ( f). Administration site will not take responsibility for any difficulty occurring outside our site.**

**      (g). Any complaint must be placed, within 24 hours counted from the occurrence**, at Customer Service Site team. Given the complexity

            and particularities of the procedure to determine the righteousness of the complaints placed after the referred 24 hour period, these shall

            only be acknowledged in cases of force majeure.

**      (h). Customer Service Site team** may, whenever deemed necessary, carefully investigate reports and other data at its disposal,

            resorting to any existing means for such effect.

**      (i). Administration website will only compensate/refund credits in the amount **proportionally determined in accordance to the price paid and

            problem effectively reported when any credit is lost due to dysfunction of our site or an Adult Service Provider in the “Nude Only” part of

            the site totally and explicitly refuses to provide erotic content. In case some erotic content is provided, Administration website will

            the situation and discretionarily decide whether any compensation/refund of credits is due. Performers of Only talk category are not allowed

            to provide any sexually explicit content or expose sexually provoking body parts even during a Private show. They must at all times wear at

            underwear  least according to their category rules.

**     (k). Only full purchased packages can be refunded.** In the event that a transaction is refunded, the correspondent amount (determined in

            accordance to the foreseen in point VI (e) above) will be credited in the credit card that was used to make the original purchase, being

            deducted from the Customer Credit Balance.

**      (l). Amounts spent on related services, such as VIP Membership, Gift or Video Rental, are not subject to refund/compensation.**

**    (m). Not with standing the referred in the previous numbers,** Administration website will not be liable for any defamatory, offensive or illegal

             conduct of any subscriber, or for any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or

             transmission,communications line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, alteration of or use of records, whether under

             contract or tort theory, or under any other cause of action, for any amount over and above the amount paid by the subscriber to our site.

**     (n). Under no circumstances, including, but not limited to, negligence, shall Our Site** or any of its related, affiliated companies be

            liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use the

            service, without prejudice of the established in the present clause.

**    (o). Cases of dishonest behavior related to online transactions** are handled with high priority keeping, however, in mind the subscriber’s

            privacy. Such cases may be outsourced to companies specialized in this field.

**     (p). In case of any fraudulent transaction Administration website reserves** the right to use all available information at its disposal during any

            kind of legal procedure. Including, without the claim of completeness, browser history, IP and e-mail addresses and any other traceable

            activity. During such legal procedures Administration website might involve other, professional investigator parties and share certain

            information in order to comply with federal law, vindicate its rights and represent the best interests of its Customers.

**     (q). Administration website grants full cooperation to legal authorities investigating fraudulent transactions** and other matters falling under

            legal jurisdiction and responds to subpoenas and court orders.
